Alright, after a long wait
our refactoring process
It's finally finished running.
Let's take a look
What changes has he made for us?
Let's take a look at the changes made at the code level.
First, he divided the original code into
divided into two major parts
The frontend part is placed in
the components directory
Then for the backend part
are all placed in this app subdirectory
Especially for the GEMINI API key in the facial cleanser APP
the use of the API key
It is placed in this folder
And inside this file,
implemented the service-oriented invocation of the large model
As you can see here
This is the call to the online model service
So it no longer directly connects to the API key on the frontend.
It's completely handed over to the backend for connection.
Moreover, the frontend and backend are implemented separately using NestJS.
implemented frontend and backend
Let's go back to the history of this conversation again
You will find that after it finishes executing
It also not only shows us the modified content
also summarized it
it tells us how to run and deploy the application later on
such an application uh
for example
First of all,
First, we'll run npm install, right
Install some necessary dependency packages
Then
add our cleansing milk API key to
add it to a local
into a local file for storing environment variables
Finally, it's time to
deploy the entire application using npm run dev
that is, to deploy it locally
So let's follow his tutorial to debug locally first
see if it can be successfully deployed
After ensuring the deployment is successful
we will then push it to the remote cloud server
to deploy it online
Okay
The first step is
We can first create a new one under the local directory
the .env.local local file
Then paste the API key of the interface into it
paste it in
So how do we obtain this API key?
We can go back we can go back to the uh
Google AI Studio
in this interface
In the lower left corner, click this button labeled 'get API key'
It will pop up an API key management interface
After we click to open it
the .local file
into this file
This way, an environment variable is prepared.
Then we click on the terminal in VS Code
Create a new terminal
Run 'npm install' in the terminal respectively
to install the necessary dependencies
and then run npm run dev
to deploy the entire application service
After the deployment is complete
When you see locally
When you see in the command line
its local access link
We click on this link
to open it in the browser
What we get is our locally deployed
such an application
you can directly engage in a conversation with it
This indicates that our application has passed the local deployment test.
Next, we can reuse
the process we introduced earlier
First, let's go back to the GitHub desktop client
what we just did in this project
modified by the large model
the modified and transformed content
push to our remote GitHub platform
Here we will briefly note
What operations have we performed in this modification?
mainly to mark
the workload of our current refactoring
Make a comment
For example
This time our modification involves separating the frontend and backend.
Hide the API key, right?
This is how it works
Then we click on commit
Then click the topmost push button
you can push the local files to our remote
into the code repository
Okay, we can check it in the code repository
refresh and take a look
Ah, you see, basically all these directories
or all these contents
have all been modified by us
have all been modified
Alright then
basically we can achieve an almost codeless
a local secondary development
The following process
in fact, it's the same process as our previous demonstration
it's exactly the same, right
Open this NETLIFY
and then deploy the project on GitHub
deploy it to the NETLIFY platform
then you can get an access link
Then you can share it with others
let them experience your application
I won't repeat the introduction here.